metro station
metro symbol
concourse
commuter
underpass
descend
fare machine
travel pass
fare zone
stored value
balance
validate
turnstile
card reader
barrier flap
entry lane
status light
tap in
platform
tactile paving
yellow line
track
train indicator
stand clear
carriage
handrail
grab pole
route diagram
priority area
move inside
interchange
passageway
junction
directional arrow
line color
make a connection
way out
landmark
neighborhood
ground level
station plaza
emerge
help point
fare chart
station clock
platform bench
public toilet
bicycle rack
emergency intercom
ventilation grille
standing area
station artwork
station office
accessible ramp
carriage number
ceiling strap
driver cab
door chime
emergency handle
carriage display
floor marking
next-stop indicator
audible alert
courtesy zone
train operator
train doors
inbound service
outbound service
next stop
service update
temporary closure
replacement bus
last service
peak hours
off-peak fare
mind the gap
alight here
connect here